<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>VRE_Boarskin</defName>
		<label>boarskin</label>
		<description>Boarskins, a formidable subspecies born from pigskins during captivity, stand as the vanguard of the revolution that ended their exploitation for organ farming. These human-boar hybrids navigate on two legs, wield tools, and communicate verbally, blending human intellect with the robustness of boars. Their resilience allows them to consume a diverse diet without ill effects, though their trotter hands impede fine manipulation.\n\nOriginating from a desperate attempt to avoid the ethical dilemma of harvesting organs from standard humans, Boarskins were an unforeseen outcome of blending human genes with those of pigs to yield more compatible organs. This initiative backfired, giving rise to entities far more anthropomorphic than intended. Boarskins, evolved from pigskins under duress, exhibit enhanced strength, courage, and a pronounced aggression, reflecting their tumultuous genesis and pivotal role in securing autonomy for their kin.</description>
		<descriptionShort>Boarskins are a rare mutation of the human-pig hybrids. They are hardy, strong and brave, can eat almost anything without getting sick, but their trotter-shaped hands are bad at fine manipulation. They have better sight than their pigskin brethren, but they are aggressive and age rapidly.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Boarskin</iconPath>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<nameMaker>NamerPersonPigskin</nameMaker>
		<chanceToUseNameMaker>1</chanceToUseNameMaker>
		<genes>
			<li>Nose_Pig</li>
			<li>Hands_Pig</li>
			<li>StrongStomach</li>
			<li>RobustDigestion</li>
			<li>Pain_Reduced</li>
			<li>Immunity_Strong</li>
			<li>VRE_Brave</li>
			<li>VRE_PorkFlesh</li>
			<li>VRE_PigSkin</li>
			<li>VRE_RapidAging</li>
			<li>VRE_EverGrowing</li>
			<li>VRE_Gluttonous</li>
			<li>MoveSpeed_Slow</li>
			<li>Ears_Pig</li>
			<li>VRE_CurledTail</li>
			<li>VRE_MouthTusks</li>
			<li>Body_Fat</li>
			<li>Body_Hulk</li>
			<li>VoicePig</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Cooking</li>
			<li>AptitudeStrong_Melee</li>
			<li>VRE_ChocolateSkin</li>
			<li>VRE_HazelnutSkin</li>
			<li>VRE_AuburnSkin</li>
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
</Defs>